So now we are going to see a valid Uid program.
So it's quite similar.
We are going to use the same circuit diagram which we used before.
The only difference is this time we have also added a buzzer.
So let me do a little zoom on it.
So the complete circuit diagram is similar.
Other than this this buzzer.
So we have added this buzzer and we have connected the high pin of buzzer with pin seven over here,
as you can see.
So all the other things like the LCD and RMF, RC 5 to 2 module using the same circuit and we are just
using this pin seven for Buzzer and we are connecting the low end of buzzer with the ground.
And we have also set up the ground as you can see.
So this is the only change in the circuit.
Let me show you the code.
So over here you can see the code.
While the code is also similar, we have defined all the things which we defined before.
The only thing here is the difference of buzzer.
We have also added the constant string buzzer on pin seven.
So over here we are defining the PIN seven, right?
And we are passing this pin on pin mode and as an output on pin seven.
As you can see.
And we are passing it on the setup, right.
And then we are over here where we are checking where we are getting the uuids.
We are also checking the Uuids so we have hardcoded this to Uids.
So these are the two uuids.
We are checking if the Uuid string is similar to this Uid or the Uid string is similar to this uid.
Then we are passing a valid Uid function.
Else we are passing the invalid Uid function and invalid and invalid Uid functions.
We are just displaying the text valid Uid and we are defining the text layers over here.
And we are also setting up the tone in buzzer with the delay of 100 milliseconds.
And an invalid function.
An invalid function.
We are also setting up the text and printing invalid uid.
And we are also setting up the buzzer tone with the delay of one second.
So this is what we have set up and clear and print functions are similar as before.
So this is the code.
Let me just upload this code and run this code.
All right, so the code uploading is done.
Now let's just place a valid measure card on our module and see what happens.
So as you can see, it's reading the card perfectly fine and it's also displaying the Uid.
Let's just place another valid ID card.
So it's also reading the other card as well.
And we have hard coded these two uuids in our code.
Right?
So it's reading only these two cards.
If we place another invalid card, let's just see what happens.
So as you can see it prints invalid card and it's also displaying the Uid of the other card.
Right.
Let's just place the valid ID card which we have hardcoded in our code one more time.
So it's reading it perfectly fine, as you can see.
So this is how we use uuids of cards to check whether the card is valid or not.
In the next video, we are going to see that how much this code is secure or whether the whether this
code is according to the industry standards or not.
And we will also see if this code is hackable or vulnerable or not.
We are going to see all those things in the coming up video.
Right.
So right now, this is how we read card and this is how we display IDs of the cards.
And in the next video, we are going to see the security of Uuids and see how much uuids are secure.